《黑镜》
《游戏测试》
(老妈)
抱歉 请您把您的设备暂时关闭
I'm gonna have to ask you to switch that off for now.
行 谢啦
Okay, thanks.
你知道这像什么吗  这有点像过山车
You know what it's kinda like? It's kinda like a rollercoaster.
懂我什么意思吗  像过山车
You know what I mean? It's like a roller coaster.
试试看 学我的动作
Try it, try it with me.
这个 这个伦敦眼有多高啊
How tall... How tall is the Eye?
这个 这个大本钟有多高啊
How tall... How tall is Big Ben?
从此之后 我就在科技记者的岗位上
Since then, I've been working as a technology correspondent
工作了两年  挺不错的
for about two years now. It's been great.
厉害啊 太牛逼了  也就是说 你做电视报道啊 什么的 之类的吧
Cool, that's awesome. So you do, like, TV reports and, like, you're like...
- 不 只做网站的 - 哦 只有网站的啊
- No, just the website. - Oh, just the website?
我的意思是 会有一些视频报道 但是主要是科技产业的东西
I mean, there's some video stuff, but tech industry pieces mainly.
哇 科技啊  真厉害  科技这玩意儿
Cool, tech. Tech's awesome. Tech's...
那你都去过哪儿了啊
So where have you been so far?
是像印第安纳·琼斯那样探索地图吗
Travelling around the map like Indiana Jones?
- 是啊 - 走遍地图上的
- Yeah. - Where the adventure line
每一条冒险旅程啊
goes zigzagging all over the place.
是啊 实际上 这趟旅程已经临近结尾了  呃
Yeah, actually, I'm almost done. Uh...
我一开始先飞到悉尼 然后去了泰国
But I started off, flew into Sydney, went to Thailand.
- 真羡慕你 - 印度
- Oh, jealous. - India. Yeah.
还去了罗马 探索了罗马
Did Rome, went to Rome.
- 整个欧洲玩了个遍 - 我都还没全去过来呢
- Did the whole Europe vacation. - Even I haven't done that.
- 真的吗 - 嗯
- Oh, really? - Mm.
棒极了  我去了西班牙的潘普洛纳
It was awesome. I went to Pamplona in Spain.
- 那儿是不是有奔牛节的 - 我也去玩了一把
- Is that where they do the bull runs? - Ran with the bulls.
- 你去跟着牛跑了吗 - 是的 我也去跑了
- You ran with the bulls? - I ran with the bulls.
- 所以给我留了个这玩意儿 - 我的天呐
- That's how I got this. - Look at that!
你还真是印第安纳·琼斯啊
You really are Indiana Jones.
你包里是不是装了鞭子和帽子啊
Have you got your whip in your bag and your hat?
我从纳粹手里拯救了世界  挺爽的
I saved the world from the Nazis. That was pretty cool.
我只是 我只是想做些以前没做过的事情
I, you know, just... trying to do, you know, shit I've never done before.
这就是你这趟旅行的初衷吗  你想要 嗯 找寻自我?
Is that what you're doing on this trip? You're, like, finding yourself?
嗯 差不多吧  我是说 我
Yeah, um... in a way. I mean, I...
我其实就是想离家里人远一点
Really to get away from the family home is what I'm doing.
哦
Oh.
嗯 这其实 这他妈挺无聊的
Yeah, that was... Whatever, that's boring.
好吧 可惜对于你这种冒险者来说
Yeah, well, I'm afraid Britain's pretty tame
英国大概算是挺没劲的吧
as far as daredevil opportunities go.
是吗  没事 反正这也是我旅途的最后一站了
Yeah? It's alright, it's the last leg of the trip anyway so...
很不幸我下周就得回去了
I'm... unfortunately home next week.
- 没什么时间 - 下周啊
- Not much time... - Next week?
- 对 - 那很快就到了啊
- Yeah. - That's not very long.
- 没错 很短 - 嗯哼
- No, it's not. - Mnh-mnh.
所以 你能告诉我这儿有什么好玩的吗
So... I could use some suggestions on fun shit to do.
- 嗯  好玩的啊 - 好玩的
- Hmm. Fun shit to do? - Fun shit to do.
嗷  嗷
Ow! Ow!
我的天呐
Jesus!
你好啊
Hello.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
哦  另一条战斗伤疤啊
Oh. Another battle scar.
差不多吧
Kind of.
让我猜猜 你是不是
Let me guess, you were, like,
在开普敦抓鲨鱼啊 伙计
totally shark fishing in Cape Town, dude.
这是你学的最像的美国口音吗
Is that your best American accent?
- 是啊 - 挺不错的啊  这个不是 嗯
- Yes. - That's pretty good. No, um...
这个是一个高中时候的混混 乔什·皮特斯给我的小礼物
It was courtesy of Josh Peters, high school dick.
我们俩在手工课的时候打起来了
He and I got into a fight in shop class.
然后他用一个 嗯 金属棍子打了我
And he hit me with this, like, metal rod thing.
真是个混球
What an arsehole.
真是个“混球”
- 你这口音学的太烂了 - 抱歉哦
- That's terrible. - I'm sorry.
你的还是我的
Is that you or me?
哦 肯定是你的
Oh, it's gotta be you.
"老妈"  真是纯美式
"Mom." You're so American.
没错
Yes, I am.
你不打算接吗
Are you not gonna get that?
好吧 这也太冷漠了
Okay, that was a little impersonal.
怎么了 你想和她聊聊吗
What, you wanna talk to her now?
- 你想和我妈聊聊吗  我可以打回去啊 - 可以啊
- You wanna talk to my mum? I'll call back. - Fair point.
还是算了吧
I don't think so.
你饿了吗
You hungry?
哇 这么多游戏  你就像个游戏工作者啊  好酷
Wow, look at all these games. You're, like, a gamer. Cool.
当然啦  我是以此为生的啊
Of course I am. For my job.
怎么 你玩街霸没被女生打哭过啊
What, a girl never beat you at Street Fighter?
这是 这是你的约会指南吗
Is this... Like, this is, like, your dating manual?
什么  《奇点》吗
What? The Singularity?
它讲了电脑智胜人类的故事 就像女人在多年之前就对男人做到的那样
It's when computers learn to outsmart man like women did years ago.
噢  哇哦
Oh! Wow!
你看 我刚刚只不过是 只是开个玩笑
See, what I was doing, it was like a joke.
- 你明白的吧 - 真的吗
- You know? - Really?
- 是啊 - 你把那个叫做玩笑啊
- Yeah. - Well, that's what you call a joke?
嗯哼  你们这儿有这种东西的吧
Mm-hmm. Yeah, you guys have those.
- 你们这儿有幽默感这种东西的吧 - 是啊 是啊  我们现在是有这玩意儿
- You guys have those here, right? - Yeah, yeah. We do at the moment.
哇
Ow!
这个笑话不错啊  不错不错
That was a good joke. That was a good joke.
享受你的马麦酱吧
Enjoy your Marmite.
哇哦  我的天
Whoa! Oh, my...
你们真的吃这鬼东西吗
Do you guys seriously eat this shit?
好吧 好吧
Okay, alright.
我妈真是救命恩人
Alright, saved by mum.
如果不想让她一个接一个电话打过来的话 最好方法
The best way to actually just stop her from calling is...
大概就是 接电话吧
I don't know, answer it.
好吧 这件事我现在有点不太想提 所以
Yeah, it's kind of like a can of worms I just don't wanna open right now, so...
她在担心你  你是她儿子  你一直在外旅游
She's worried. You're her son. You've been travelling,
我想 如果你和她聊聊的话 可能
and I just think if you speak to her, then...
嗯 我 我在锡拉丘兹还和她住在一起
Yeah, well, I still live at home with her back in Syracuse.
- 没事啊  挺好的啊 - 嗯
- That's cool. That's fine. - Yeah.
我在照顾我爸
I was taking care of my dad.
哦  他还好吧
Oh, shit. Is he...?
不 他去世了
No, he died.
- 我的天呐  我很抱歉 - 他去年走的  没事的
- Oh, my God. I'm sorry. - Last year. No, it's okay.
我们之前就知道了  是早发型老年痴呆症
It was coming for a while. It was early onset Alzheimer's.
哦 那肯定很 呃 难熬
Oh, that must have been really... uh... tough.
嗯 他是我最好的朋友
Yeah, he was my best friend.
有时候他就这么看着我 也不知道我是谁
Sometimes he'd just look at me and wouldn't even know who I was.
我妈呢 我根本不 我甚至不知道怎么和她开口
Well, my mum, like, I don't even... I don't know how to talk to her.
我们缺了那个连接点  我都不知道从哪儿说起
You know, I don't have that connection. I don't even know where to start.
所以我就离开家了  这就是我踏上旅途的原因
So that's why I left. That's why I went on this trip.
只是想离开家 为自己多创造一点回忆
Just to get away and make, you know, all the memories that I can...
在我还能这么做的时候
while I can.
我知道我必须和她谈谈 我必须
And I know I gotta talk to her and I gotta just...
但是不能是在电话上谈  你知道 我得当面解决
But not on this. You know, I just... I'll deal with it.
等我回家了我会当面和她谈谈  我只是
I'll deal with it when I get back, you know. I'll just...
你是个好人 库珀
You're a good guy, Cooper.
给你妈妈打电话吧
Call your mum.
(卡内余额不足   请取回您的卡)
零 零 一 九 三 九 二 九
Zero, zero, one, nine, three, nine, two, nine.
不 我昨晚没在苏梅岛买凉鞋
No, I did not buy a pair of sandals in Koh Samui last night
因为我在
because I'm in...
那要花多久
And how long does that take?
因为我要买一张回美国的机票
Because I need to buy a ticket back to America.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
我告诉你 这是我听过的最厚颜无耻的第二次约会的借口了
Can I just say, this is the most blatant cover story for a second hook-up ever?
太好了  太好了  我的天  谢谢你 谢谢 谢谢
Yes! Yes! Oh, my God. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
好吧  别忘了你的包
Alright. Don't forget your bag.
我的包 对对 我的包  太好了  你真是溜
The bag, yep, my bag. Alright. You are a top bird.
我不知道这句话是什么意思 但是我有次听别人用过 你绝对符合形容
I don't know what that means, but I heard somebody say it once, and you're it.
我有个计划
I got a plan.
呃  差不多是临时工吧
Yeah. It's odd jobs.
- 给谁打工啊 - 给 嗯 是用一个软件
- For who? - For, like, it's an app.
你差不多可以 大概 我之前没钱的时候也用过这玩意儿找临时工 所以
You can kind of... like, I've used it all over when funds were low, so...
- 有些还真有意思 - 挺酷的吧
- Oh, there's some interesting ones. - Pretty cool.
- “需要找刺激的人” - 噢
- "Thrillseekers wanted." - Ooh.
- 似乎正合你胃口啊 - 好吧
- This looks right up your street. - Okay.
报酬等级是四星  真是高价  不错啊
Okay, four pound signs. That's a biggie. That's good.
差不多要出城了啊
It's a little out of town.
是个游戏试玩 这个公司叫什么斋拓
And some kind of play test deal for a company called Saitoo...
斋拓由
Saitogoo...
- 斋藤游戏吧 - 斋藤游戏  没错
- SaitoGemu? - SaitoGemu. Yeah.
是个大公司啊
They're huge.
- 很大的公司 - 是吗
- They're really big. - Really?
- 恐怖游戏啊 - 呃
- Horror games? - Uh...
你有没有听说过 嗯 哪个是他们的来着
Have you heard of... Oh, what's one of theirs?
- 哈莱克之影 - 哈莱克之影  我有那游戏
- Harlech Shadow. - Harlech Shadow? Yes, I have.
我以前总在我兄弟戴维·路德维希的地下室里玩
I used to play that in my buddy David Ludwig's basement
大概是我们七年级的时候
when we were, like, seventh grade.
那就是斋藤翔  是他的公司
Well, that's Shou Saito. It's his company.
- 他是个超级天才 深藏不露 - 好吧
- He's like this genius, super secretive. - Okay.
很明显 他们在开发新项目
And apparently, they're working on this new project.
牵涉的资金巨大  突破以往  但没人知道任何信息
Big money involved. Groundbreaking. But nobody knows anything about it.
好吧 如果我运筹帷幄 我能从翔那给你弄个独家消息
Well, maybe if I play my cards right I can get you an exclusive with Shou.
嗯  为你的游戏柜加点料  如何
Hmm? For Shelf? Hmm?
你应该拍下来
You should take a photo.
说真的 如果你拍到他们正在弄的任何东西
Seriously, if you get a photo of anything that they're working on,
那值的钱可比那四星级的报酬多多了啊
that's a fuckload more money than four pound signs.
酷
Cool.
这个地方在哪
Well, where is this place?
科珀先生
Mr. Copper.
噢 嗨  嗯 叫我库珀就行了
Oh, hi. Um... Just Cooper.
库珀先生 我道歉
Mr. Cooper, I apologize.
叫我库珀就可以了
Just Cooper is fine.
那么这样的话 叫我卡蒂就行了
Then, in that case, I'm just Katie.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 跟我来 - 噢好
- Follow me. - Oh, yeah.
- 我拿下我的背包 - 拉夫会帮你拿的
- I'll just get my pack here. - Rav will take care of that.
噢 拉夫会拿的  好极了
Oh, Rav will take care of that. Okay, great.
真好  我也不想到处背来背去
That's good. I don't wanna carry it anyway.
拉夫让我想起那些终极大boss
Rav kind of reminds me of like an end-of-level boss.
你知道的 龟派气功波  就
You know, haiukon. Just...
- 你的旅行怎么样 - 很好  多谢关心
- How was your journey? - Great. Thanks.
- 接车一切顺利吗 - 顺利
- The car pick you up okay? - Yeah.
哇
Wow.
这边
This way.
他们在看什么东西吗  酷啊  真酷
Are they... seeing? It's cool. Very cool.
哇
Wow.
来
Come on.
感觉我要见邓布利多了  希望我能进格兰芬多
Feel like I'm gonna go meet Dumbledore. Hope I get Gryffindor.
我需要你交出手机或者一切能收发信息的通讯设备
I'm gonna need your phone and anything else you might use to send and receive.
- 有点偏执 不觉得吗 - 小心点总没错
- A little paranoid, don't you think? - Can't be too careful.
好的 走吧
Okay, there you go.
哇 你还真是偏执得很啊  哇
Wow, you really are paranoid. Whoa!
好白啊
It's white.
呃
Um...
这上面的意思是说 我同意割肾吗
Okay, so I'm guessing this says, like, I agree to have my kidneys harvested?
实际上这是份标准保密协议
Actually, it's a pretty standard NDA-disclaimer thing.
好吧
Okay.
重要的是你得知道游戏过程中包含一个小型的医疗程序
It's important that you realize there is a small medical procedure involved.
抱歉 不是游戏测试吗
Sorry, for a game?
不是永久性的 我们也不会要割你的肾
Nothing permanent and we don't harvest your kidneys,
- 我保证 - 好吧
- I promise. - Okay.
比你打个耳洞还要小的动静
It's no more invasive than having your ears pierced.
“保密信息 大脑下载
"Confidential information, brain downloads
游戏内容 时长 终止”
the game, duration, termination..."
呃 签名页
Um... The signature page...
- 我在哪儿签字 - 哦
- Where do I sign? - Oh.
- 签名  嗯 - 缺了一页
- Signature. Yeah. - There's a page missing.
- 好吧 - 请等一下
- Okay. - Just a moment.
好吧  我就在这儿 等着
Alright. I'll just wait... here.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
- 一切都好吗 - 都好
- All good? - All good.
我们正在开发一项增强交互的现实系统
What we're working on is an interactive augmented reality system.
- 像是虚拟现实的那种吗 - 更像是高于现实的层面
- Like VR? - More like layers on top of reality.
哦
Oh.
好吧  呃
Okay. Um...
哇哦
Ow.
呃
Um...
- 那是什么 - 我们把这个叫做蘑菇
- What's that? - We call this a mushroom.
- 马里奥兄弟吃的那种吗 - 你要这么想的话
- Like Mario Brothers? - If you like.
- 你是有资格做这个的 对吧 - 我手里倒是还没死过人
- You're qualified to do this, right? - I haven't killed anyone yet.
能开始了吗
May I?
好的
Yeah.
完成了
All done.
- 就这样嘛 - 我说了我很厉害的
- That was it? - See, I told you I'm good.
- 没事 别担心 这不是永久性的 - 呃
- No, don't worry, it's not permanent. - Um...
好吧  这是什么啊 是某种记忆测试之类的东西吗
Okay. What is this, like, some kind of memory test or something like that?
- 你会知道的 - 哦 好吧
- You'll find out. - Oh, okay.
启动的时候你可能会感觉有一点刺痛
You might feel a slight twinge as it initializes.
哦 好的
Oh, okay.
5:38启动
Commencing at 5:38.
- 你准备好了吗 - 是的长官
- You ready? - Yes, sir!
差不多了
Nearly there.
我记得我关了啊
I thought I turned that off.
- 完成了  感觉还好吗 - 嗯哼
- All done. You feel okay? - Uh-huh.
感觉不错啊
Feel great.
- 看着这几个目标点 - 好的
- Watch the targets. - Okay.
呃
Um...
这
Is...
你看见了什么
What do you see?
像是个 呃
Like a... um...
电子游戏里的地鼠
Like a video game gopher.
- 细节是不是更清晰了 - 是的
- Is it more detailed now? - Yeah.
没错 是的
Yep, yeah.
- 现在呢 - 我了个大槽
- And now? - Holy fuck!
我去  这也 卧槽  他就在
Holy shit! He... Fuck. He's right...
他就这么 他真是在 我能不能
He's right... He's right... Can I...
呼
Whoo!
他并不是真实存在的  这只是个精神投影
He's not real. He's a sort of mental projection.
- 你看得见他  我看不见 - 你看不见吗
- You can see him. I can't. - You can't?
哇哦  哦 好吧
Wow! Oh, okay.
打它
Give him a whack.
打这玩意儿吗  哦  好 好吧
Give him a whack? Oh. Okay, alright.
来吧  嗯 就像是打地鼠吗
Okay! Alright, so just like whack-a-mole.
- 嗯哼 - 我可是玩了上千万次了啊  来吧
- Mm-hmm. - I've played it a million times. Okay.
很好
Alright.
上吧  继续来啊
Here we go. Come on up.
哦  你会从哪儿出来呢
Oh! Where you coming up?
不  不
No. No.
不
No.
噢
Oh!
好吧  别上来哦
Alright. Stay down.
哦  好吧
Oh! Okay.
真棒  太牛逼了  你真可爱
Good game. Very good game. You are so adorable.
好了 再见吧  拜
Okay, bye. Bye.
- 就这样了吗 - 是的
- Is that it? - Afraid so.
哦
Oh.
那么 你看到的地鼠是二维的还是三维的
Now, were the gophers two-dimensional or three?
三维  不 不 不  3D 超级3D  像是 嗯哼
Three. No, no, no. 3D, super 3D. Like... Yeah.
- 这只是个限量版测试demo - 这是个demo？
- Now this is just a limited test demo. - That was a demo?
我觉得你能够做我们这个实验的beta测试了
I think you should beta test the full experience we're working on.
当然了 会有更多的报酬  如果你打算玩下去的话
There'd be more money in it, of course. If you're game?
当然啦 嗯哼 我肯定要玩的  我要继续
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh-huh, I'm game. I'm game.
- 这位就是斋藤胜 - 噢
- This is Shou Saito. - Oh!
- 你就是我们最新的志愿者了吧 - 嗨
- You must be our latest volunteer. - Hi.
这真是太厉害了  你好啊
This is really great. Hi.
你好
Hi.
我只想说 我只想说 那个打地鼠游戏 超级好玩
I just... I wanted to say that the mole game, super fun.
超级好玩 好玩
Super fun... fun.
- 好玩? - 好玩
- Fun? - Fun.
- 好玩是好的 - 对  嗯
- Fun is good. - Yeah. Oh.
- 玩游戏是好的 - 嗯
- Playing games is good. - Mm.
你的心跳会加速
Your heart goes faster.
- 你会笑 - 对
- You smile. - Yeah.
对  或者 呃 尖叫
Yeah. Or, um... scream.
噢
Oh!
我喜欢让玩家吓一跳
I have always liked to make the player jump.
恐惧  你害怕了 你吓一跳
Frightened. You get scared, you jump.
- 之后 你感觉很爽 - 对
- Afterwards, you feel good. - Yeah.
你会感受到喜悦
You glow.
为什么
Why?
哦 呃
Oh, um...
因为肾上腺素急升
Because of the adrenaline rush.
- 对 - 没错
- Yes. - Yeah.
但是最主要是因为你还活着
But mostly because you are still alive.
你在一个安全的环境里面对了你最深的恐惧
You have faced your greatest fears in a safe environment.
它能释放你的恐惧  能让你自由
It is a release of fear. It liberates you.
对  没错 我太同意了
Yeah. I mean, totally.
我们现在正在开发一款
What we are working on now
史上最个性定制化的生存恐怖游戏
is the most personal survival horror game in history.
有意思
Cool.
这款游戏能通过你自己的思想 找出你最害怕的东西
One that works out how to scare you by using your own mind.
哇哦  这 这听起来真的是太疯狂了
Whoa. That... That sounds crazy.
我已经迫不及待了
Can't wait!
我正在上传一个神经网络包
I'm uploading a neural net package.
神经网络包 神经网 嗯
Neural net packing, neural net. Hmm.
这名字可能会有点儿效果  都是90年代的词
Name could use a little work, I think. It's all 90s.
开玩笑的 这是个好名字
I'm just kidding, it's a good name.
这是目前最尖端的人工智能技术
It's state of the art intelligence software.
它能在运行中边学习边自我改写  它可以监测脑部活动
It learns and adapts on the fly. It'll monitor your brain activity
从而计算出怎样才能最大程度地惊吓你
and try and work out how best to frighten you
然后根据你的经历而做出调整
and then adjust to your experience accordingly.
哇哦
Whoa!
- 你准备好了吗 - 准备好了
- Are you ready? - Oh, yeah.
- 把我传送上去 我们开始吧 准备射击 - 闭上眼睛
- Beam me up. Here we go, lock and load. - Eyes closed.
- 现在的时间是下午6时17分 - 好的
- Time is currently 6:17 p.m. - Okay.
正在上传中  五 四 三 二 一
It's uploading. Five, four, three, two, one.
你现在有什么感觉
How are you feeling?
呃
Um...
我感觉不错  挺正常的
I feel good. I feel normal.
好的 慢慢站起来
Okay. Stand up, slowly.
你准备好开始游戏了吗
Are you ready to play?
这不是哈莱克之影里面的房子吗
Isn't this the Harlech Shadow house?
这是那房子的一部分
It's part of the estate.
这其实是猎场管理员的小屋  但是 对 就是按照游戏里建造的
The gamekeeper's lodge, actually. But, yeah, this was the model.
这里的布局和游戏中的一样 包括质地纹理也都一样
The layout was replicated for the game and the texture scanned.
哇
Wow!
真的是 太酷了
Very, very cool.
游戏内容是什么 我该做什么
So what's the game, what do I do?
你不需要做任何事
You don't have to do anything.
你只要一个人呆在这里
You just stay in here alone,
看你可以坚持多久 直到你害怕得无法继续为止
see how long you last until you're too scared to continue.
所以我只要呆在这里就行了吗
So all I have to do is, like, stay here?
而且还能拿到钱吗
And I get paid for that?
我要回控制室了 我会在那儿监控这里
I'll be back in the control room, watching.
这里到处都是摄像头 所以不要偷那些银质餐具
There are cameras all over, so no stealing the silverware.
戴上这个
And now there's this.
- 这是什么 - 是耳机
- And what's this? - It's an earpiece.
噢
Oh!
对 戴上这个 我们就可以保持联络了
Yeah, just pop it in, and you and I will be in contact the whole time.
噢 有意思
Oh, cool.
所以我对你说话 你就能听到吗  太棒了
And I can, like, talk to you, and you'll hear it? Great, that's great.
记住 你看到的所有东西 都不可能对你造成身体上的伤害
Now, nothing you'll see can physically harm you.
这只是视觉和听觉效果 就像之前的打地鼠游戏
It's all just audio-visual, like the gopher game.
噢 好的
Oh, okay.
但是 如果情况太激烈的话 我们会随时叫停
But if it does get too intense, we can pull you out at any time
- 结束实验 - 好的
- and stop the experiment. - Okay.
你能想一个安全词吗
Is there a safe word you can think of?
就算在危难关头 也能简单想起的单词 有吗
Something easy to remember in distress?
“停”这个词怎么样
How about the word "stop"?
- 不错  就喊“停”吧 - 嗯
- Good choice. "Stop" it is. - Yeah.
好的 那你就自己好好享受吧
Okay, we'll leave you to enjoy your evening.
- 好的 - 你会在几分钟后听到我的声音
- Alright. - You'll hear from me in a moment.
不用客气
Just make yourself at home.
好的 好的  放松点
Okay, all right. Well, take her easy.
哈莱克之影啊
Harlech... Shadow.
这是真的吗  对 这是真的 是真的 是真的死了
Is this real? Yeah, it's real. That's real. It's really dead.
- 库珀 - 噢 嗨
- Cooper. - Oh, hey.
- 你听到我说话了吗 - 一清二楚
- Are you hearing me? - Loud and clear.
噢
Oh!
看起来你已经打算开始喝酒啦
Reaching for the Dutch courage already, I see.
- 不好意思 这红酒里不含酒精 - 没意思
- I'm afraid that wine's non-alcoholic. - Lame.
- 我们需要你保持清醒的头脑 - 好吧  有道理
- Well, we need you with a clear head. - Okay. Fair point. Fair point.
这件工艺品质量很好  真是太棒了
This is high-quality craftsmanship. This is nice.
雕刻得很细腻
Yeah. It's good woodwork.
- 这幅画中就是这栋屋子 - 观察力不错
- That's this place. - Full marks for observation.
没错  太棒了
Mm-hmm! Yep!
好的 挺爽的
Alright, there we go.
啊
Ah!
- 该死 - 怎么了
- Oh, shit. - What's up?
我老是忘记我没带手机
I just forgot I don't have my phone.
我一直习惯性地伸手拿手机 完全忘记我根本就没带手机
I keep going for it, I forget it's not in my pocket.
而这里也没有电视 所以说
And there's, uh... no TV here, so...
欢迎来到十九世纪  没有电视 没有互联网 没有Wi-Fi
Welcome to the 19th century. No TV, no Internet, no wi-fi.
好吧 难怪人们老是看见鬼鬼怪怪
Yeah. No wonder people were seeing shit.
他们可能是无聊得发疯了
Probably were just bored out of their gourds.
对 那也是对人们见到鬼怪的主导解释
Well, that's the leading theory about ghost sightings.
当缺乏刺激时 人的意识会作祟
The mind plays tricks when less stimulated.
那时人们的消遣方式很少 所以他们常常能看到鬼怪
Fewer distractions, people saw more ghosts.
谢谢你告诉我
Isn't that a nice piece of info?
至少他们还有书看
Well, they got literature, though.
太贴心了 不是吗
That's pretty sweet, right?
天 我都想不起来我上一次看书是什么时候了
Oh, my God, I can't remember the actual last time that I read a book.
但人们过去常常阅读
To think people used to do this on purpose.
我知道的  这很疯狂  但是为什么呢
I know. Crazy. Why?
- 我并不认为我 - 安静点 好吗
- You know, I don't think I've... - Shh, alright?
我要研究下这个老古董  我需要专注
I need to get into some old-school shit here. Concentrate.
对不起
Pardon me.
你的心率正在逐渐上升
Can I point out your heart rate just increased?
对 可能是因为这里有一只巨大的蜘蛛
Yeah. Well, it should have cos there's a huge crazy spider.
你看到蜘蛛了吗
You see a spider?
- 难道你 难道你看不到它吗 - 看不到
- You don't... you don't see that? - No.
不要 不要过来 不要
Don't... Don't walk. Don't...
该死的
Holy shit!
像你这样的硬汉 居然会害怕蜘蛛
Tough guy like you, scared of spiders.
我只是不喜欢蜘蛛而已
Yeah, I'm just not fond of them.
所以系统很快就发现 你害怕蜘蛛
It's worked out you're an arachnophobe quickly.
系统正在寻找你的弱点
It's probing for weak spots.
该死的
God damn it.
去死吧
Fucker!
太好了
Yeah!
呃
Um...
好吧
Okay.
太棒了 哈哈
Yeah, well, yeah.
这可比刚刚的打地鼠游戏真实多了
Whole lot more realistic than the gopher game.
很真实  图像处理得很不错
It's good. It's good graphics.
太真实了 呃 嗯
It's good, uh... Yeah.
真特么辣鸡
Weak sauce.
- 怎么了 - 只是
- What is it? - Just...
没什么 没什么
Nothing. Nothing.
在这幅画里面 这里有  不 这里有灯光
Here with the figures. There's a... No. There's a light on...
有光在
now, in the...
你可以 拉近镜头  拉近镜头看一下这幅画吗
Can you... zoom in and... Zoom in on it?
那样你就能看到我说的了  哇
And you can see what I'm talking about. Whoa!
- 库珀 - 现在又出现了  嘘
- Cooper... - And now there's... Shh!
窗户里有一个人  而那不是
There's a guy in the window. That wasn't...
对了
Yeah.
他又消失了  窗户里没人了
And now he's gone. Now nobody's in the window.
那是
Which is the...
嗯 那里有一个
Yeah, there's a...
只是漏水的管道而已
Just leaky pipes.
我就知道  只是漏水的管道而已
I knew it. It was leaky pipes, like...
噢该死
Holy fuck!
该死
Fuck!
噢  噢
Oh! Oh!
好吧
Okay.
这真的吓到我了  你吓到我了
That got me. You got me.
你看到了什么
What are you seeing?
一个诡异该死的人
Like a creepy fucking guy.
哇 只是
Wow, just...
噢 我的天哪  噢 我的天哪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
他看起来好像乔什·彼得斯
He kinda looks like Josh Peters.
- 这是乔什·彼得斯  你是乔什·彼得斯 - 你在说什么
- It's Josh Peters! You're Josh Peters! - Sorry?
你是高中的乔什·彼得斯  是我在高中认识的一个人
You're Josh Peters from high school! From a guy I know at high school.
系统可能挖掘了你的记忆 创造出了这个形象
The system could be mining some of your personal memories for texture.
你害怕乔什·彼得斯吗
Was Josh Peters someone you were scared of?
他就是个恶霸  我不怕他
He was a bully. I wasn't scared.
我不害怕他  但他是个恶霸 而且
I wasn't scared of him,  but he was a bully and...
嘿小子  我学过一点以色列防身术 我准备好了
Man! Take a couple of Krav Maga classes and I'd be ready.
我准备好了
I'd be ready!
来打我啊 哈
Kali ma! Dah!
我要喝点酒  振作一下
I'm gonna get some wine. Re-up.
我也可以给你来点酒 但你喝不了
I'd offer you some, but I don't think you can drink it so...
待会儿见 彼得斯
Catch ya later, Peters.
这款无酒精的葡萄酒还挺好喝的
This non-alcoholic wine is pretty good.
虽然我不是这方面的专家 但的确挺好喝的
I'm not like a expert or anything, but it's kinda great.
我在法国的时候  我住在一个类似葡萄园的地方
I was in France. I stayed at this, like, vineyard,
他们好像是在 踩葡萄节上 喝这种酒
and they had this wine, like, grape-stomping festival.
那种酒很棒  我知道
Now that, that wine was good. I know that.
你一直在东拉西扯
You're being discursive.
- 什么叫东拉西扯啊  东拉西扯 - 就是话多
- What is discursive? Discursive? - Talkative.
- 嗯 - 乱扯
- Mm-hmm. - Rambling.
有什么问题吗
Is that a problem?
人害怕的时候会变得多话
People sometimes talk more when they're afraid.
有助于缓解恐惧
Helps compensate for the fear.
- 也可以掩饰恐惧 - 哦是吗
- Masks it, too. - Oh, yeah?
就像你深更半夜打开电视机
Similar to when you've got the TV on late at night.
电视机的声音能让你不那么孤单
The voices make you feel less alone.
尽管你孤身一人
Even though you are alone.
你没有吓到我 卡蒂
You aren't scaring me, Katie.
遗憾
Pity.
这儿有冰箱吗
Is there like a refrigerator here?
橱柜里有些零食
There's some snacks in the cupboard.
好嘞  一只青蛙两条
Alrighty. Eenie meenie, miney...
腿  好嘞
Mo! Alright.
好的 姜味饼干
Okay, ginger snaps.
我看看
Let's see.
好好好  可以吃
Yeah, yeah, yeah. This'll do.
接下来 嗯
Now... um...
当我关上这扇门 他就会出现在门后 是吗
He's gonna be right behind this door when I close it, isn't he?
没错 系统就是这么运作的
Yeah, that's how this works.
早知道了  突然跳出来吓人已经是个老招数了
Knew it. Jump scares get pretty old...
我操
Fuck!
哦天哪
Oh, God.
- 那是什么鬼 - 你看到了什么
- What the hell is that? - What do you see?
操他妈的
Holy shit!
这特么是 呃
A fucking... Uh...
难以描述
Hard to explain.
就像是个长着人脸的超级大蜘蛛 嘴里吐着鸡巴
It's like a huge-ass spider with a face and dicks coming out of his mouth.
是
It's...
是彼得斯  彼得斯在里面
Peters. Peters is inside.
像是蜘蛛和彼得斯的混合物
Like a Peters-spider mash-up.
啊 卡蒂  这是你干的吗 还是我自己设想出来的
Ah, Katie! Are you doing this, or is this fucking me?
- 我想这都是因为你自身的恐惧 - 真操蛋
- I think that's all you. - I'm so fucked up!
天哪  我操
God! Fuck!
操你妈的 你真特么恶心
Holy shit, you're fucking gross.
喂
Yeah...
不好意思 你能再说一遍吗
Sorry, can you say again?
卡蒂 在吗
Katie, hello?
我操 卡蒂
Damn it, Katie!
当你重新上线的时候 出个声就好
Whenever you come back online, just say the word.
不 我不害怕 只是有点 无聊
No, I'm not scared, just... bored.
是你们吗
That you guys?
过来修耳机吗  这大概是个好主意
Coming to fix the earpiece? That's probably a good idea.
嗯  嗯
Yeah. Yeah.
我操 老兄
Fuck it, man!
来吧
Come on!
你现在很危险
You're in danger.
索尼娅
Sonja?
你居然能与我对话  好吧 真是不可思议
Now we're talking. Alright, this is incredible.
这 真是神奇  令我印象深刻
This... very impressive. I am thoroughly impressed.
我 哇  哇
I am... Wow! Wow!
你看起来如此真实  你就像她本人一样
You look so real. You're, like, just like her.
我是说 哇
I mean, wow.
只不过 很不幸你不 嗯
Except... you're just unfortunately not... um...
- 库珀 你在干什么 - 等等  等一下 等一下
- Cooper, what are you doing? - Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on.
- 库珀 你很危险 - 嘘  安静  安静  我得想一想
- Cooper, you're in danger. - Shh! Quiet. Quiet! I need to think.
你真特么真实  你好真实  你好真实
You're fucking real. You are real. You're real.
- 库珀 你很 - 你是索尼娅  你真的在这里
- Cooper, you're in... - You're Sonja. You're actually here.
- 你现在真的在这里是吗 - 我是真实的  我真的在这里
- Are you actually here right now? - I'm real. I'm actually here.
- 天呐 - 而且我们必须得走
- God. - And we have to go.
- 你得听我说 - 你怎么在这
- You have to listen to me. - How are you here?
记得你传给我的那张照片吗
You know that photo that you sent me?
我查了一下 斋藤翔去年申请了一项
I dug around and apparently Shou Saito took out a patent
有关计算机与人脑接口的专利
for a computer brain interface last year.
你怎么会是真的  我不
How are you real? I don't...
好吧 妈的  我不
Okay, fuck. I don't...
他们带你来这儿了
They brought you here!
你是 你是真的 而他们带你来这儿了
You are, you're real, and they brought you here,
他们想搞我  做得好 做得妙
and they're trying to fuck with me. Nice try, good try.
我明白了  这是试验的一部分
I get it. It's part of the test.
但他的专利申请被拒绝了  他们说这实验太疯狂 太危险
His patent got rejected outright. They said it was insane, it was dangerous.
喔  真的吗  他们付你多少钱
Wow. Really? How much are they paying you?
真的  因为你现在正在毁掉这氛围
Honestly. Cos you're killing it right now.
- 他们给你什么东西了吗 - 抱歉 我以为你是假的
- Have they given you something? - Sorry, I thought you were fake.
但现在我知道了你是真的 我应该好好招待你的
But now I know you're real, I'm being a really terrible host.
我有些不含酒精的葡萄酒  或许能够增加气氛
I got some non-alcoholic wine. Might put us in the mood.
- 库珀 我想说的是 - 我们去厨房说
- Cooper, what I want to do is... - We'll talk about it in the kitchen.
- 库珀 - 索尼娅 放松点 好吗
- Cooper! - Sonja, relax, okay?
放弃吧  我知道 一切都完蛋了 好吗  随它去吧
Give it up. I know, the jig's up, okay? Let it go.
听着 库珀 还有更多
Look, Cooper, there's more.
去年有五个人失踪了
Five people have disappeared in the past year.
全部都是游客 全都注册了那个古怪愚蠢的找工作应用
All tourists, all registered with that stupid odd jobs app.
哦 是吗  喔  天啊 疯了
Oh, yeah? Wow. God, that's crazy.
不管他们在对你做什么 不管他们对你做了什么
Whatever they're doing to you, whatever they've done to you,
很危险 我们真的得走 立刻 库珀
it's dangerous, and we really have to go now, Cooper.
好的 好  好吧
Okay, okay. Alright.
- 如果你的故事是真的 - 库珀
- Well, if your story's true... - Cooper.
- 那么你是怎么找到我的 - 什么
- Then how'd you find me? - What?
你怎么知道我在这里的
How'd you know where I am?
这是个游戏公司 我查了地址
It's a games company, I looked up the address.
是啊 真的吗
Yeah, really?
不 不 不 不  你是怎么在这里找到我的  这个地方
No, no, no, no. How'd you find me here? This place.
- 我跟踪了你 - 你跟踪了我
- I tracked you. - You tracked me?
是啊 通过你手机的GPS  “找到他”应用
Yeah, with your GPS on your phone. Find My Friends.
“找到他”  你就唬我吧 他们收走了我的手机
Find My Friends? That would've worked, but they took my phone.
我的手机在一英里外的地方  是啊 你说得倒挺真的
And it's in a building, like, a mile away. So, yeah, nice try.
对
That's right.
女性比男性聪明吗 也不过如此  奇点什么的鬼
So much for women outsmarting men. Singularity that!
听着 我想说的就是
Look, all I'm saying is that
我觉得你还能编出更好的故事
I think that you could've come up with a better story,
更有趣的故事 或者是
it could have been funny or...
好的 好吧 别生气
Okay, alright, don't be pissed.
你知道你的银行账号是怎么被盗的吗
Do you ever wonder how your bank account got hacked?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
- 我趁你睡着的时候复制了你的卡 - 喔  好的
- I cloned your card as you were asleep. - Whoa. Okay.
放下刀  你拿那个要做什么
Put the knife down. What are you going to do with that?
是我让你注意到这份工作的
I drew your attention to this job.
索尼娅 把那把刀放下 好吗  这不好笑
Sonja, put the fucking knife down, okay? It's not funny.
你本该打给你妈妈的 库珀
Should've called your mum, Cooper.
- 但是你打给了我 而我把你带到这里 - 索尼娅
- But you called me, and I led you here... - Sonja.
- 你知道吗 - 就像在路上撒上面包屑 把你引来
- You know what? - ...like a breadcrumb trail.
放下刀  停下  好了 我是认真的 放下刀 索尼娅
Put the knife down. Drop the act. Okay, seriously, drop the knife, Sonja.
一点都他妈不好笑  放下刀
It's not fucking funny. Put the knife...
我报名的不是这种活动  我他妈玩够了 好吗
This isn't what I signed up for. I'm fucking done, okay?
草
Fuck!
什么鬼
What the fuck?
操  哦
Oh, fuck! Oh!
麻痹
Holy fuck!
停
Stop!
草
Fuck!
妈的  妈的
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
- 库珀 - 卡蒂
- Cooper. - Katie!
- 卡蒂 - 库珀
- Katie! - Cooper.
- 卡蒂 - 库珀 发生什么了
- Katie! - Cooper, what's happening?
他妈的发生什么了
What the fuck happened?
发生什么了  我们刚刚一直在说话  但是你一直没有回应
What's happening? We've been talking. You've not been responding.
- 你说过我什么都不会感觉到的 - 你看见什么了  那里有什么
- You said I wouldn't feel anything! - What are you seeing? What's there?
- 草  她现在消失了 - 谁消失了
- Fuck! She's gone now. - Who's gone?
哦 我的天 我 我感觉到它了
Oh, my God, I-I felt it.
一把刀捅进了我的胳膊啊
There's a knife in my arm!
- 在我肩膀上 - 库珀 刚刚那是谁
- In my shoulder. - Cooper, who was there?
- 操 索尼娅 - 谁
- Fuck... Sonja. - Who?
索尼娅  一个我认识的女孩 麻痹  她捅了我
Sonja. She's this girl that I know, that fucking... She stabbed me.
- 她拿了一把刀 - 没有东西可以伤害到你 库珀
- She had a fucking knife. - Nothing can harm you, Cooper.
- 不 不 不 不  她有实体 - 不 她不可能有
- No, no, no, no. She was solid. - No, she can't have been.
她 我被捅了啊  我当然知道
She... I was stabbed! I would know!
你看到的任何东西都不可能伤害你 甚至是接触你
Nothing you see can harm or even touch you.
一切都只是视听效果
It's purely audio-visual.
- 没有实际的感觉 - 妈的  有 有啊
- There's no physical sensation. - Fuck! Yes, there was!
- 库珀 你得冷静下来 - 我知道 因为我感觉到了 好吗
- Cooper, you need to calm down. - I know because I felt it, okay?
我感觉到了她的胳膊 是温的
I felt her arm, it was warm,
而且我感觉到她麻痹用刀捅了我的肩膀
and I felt her fucking stab me in the shoulder.
- 这不可能 - 哦 我天
- That's not possible. - Oh, my God.
- 不可能的 库珀 - 是的 就是这样  是的 是这样的
- It's not possible, Cooper. - Yeah, it is! Yeah, it is!
不可能有躯体感觉的
Physical sensations shouldn't be possible.
- 除非 我的意思是 - 哦 我天  除非什么
- Unless, I mean... - Oh, God. Unless what?
我不知道  神经元网络可能找到了
I don't know. The neuron net, it could have maybe worked out
复制躯体感受过的经历的方法
some means of replicating physical experiences,
- 但这是史无前例的 - 老天爷啊
- but that would be unprecedented. - Jesus Christ.
好吧 你知道吗  停下这游戏
Okay, you know what? Stop the game.
我想退出  立刻让我离开
I want out. Just pull me out now.
停 停 停  安全词  快他妈停下来
Stop, stop, stop. Safe word. Fucking stop!
- 好的 好的 让我们处理一下 - 哦 天啊
- Okay, okay, just let us work it out. - Oh, God.
不行 我想立刻退出这鬼游戏
No, I want this fucking thing out now.
库珀 不要试图自己移除那装置
Cooper, do not attempt to remove that yourself.
自己移除装置是极其危险的
Removing it yourself is extremely dangerous.
停下来 那可能会杀了你
Stop that, that could kill you!
保持冷静就好
Just stay calm!
那是翔吗
Is that Shou?
那是翔吗  他说什么呢  他说什么呢
Is that Shou? What's he saying? What's he saying?
好吧 库珀  我们即将停止游戏
Okay, Cooper. We're gonna commence with deactivation.
哦 那是好消息
Oh, that's great news.
我们需要你跟随指令 直到你到达接入点
We need you to follow instructions and make it to the access point.
接入点 非常好  那该死的接入点在哪里
The access point? Great. Where the fuck's the access point?
- 哦 操  怎么还有台阶啊 喂 - 再上一层楼就好了
- Oh, fuck! More stairs? Come on! - Just one more level.
- 相信我 - 好的
- Trust me. - Okay.
上面一层的右手边
Left at the top.
- 好 哪扇门 - 尽头的房间
- Okay, which door? - Room at the end.
怎么了
What is it?
那扇门后面肯定有什么东西  我能感觉到
There's gonna be something behind there. I can feel it.
- 比如 - 比如什么
- Something like... - Like what?
个性定制的破烂恐怖玩意儿
Some personal fucked-up shit.
比如 我不知道 我能感觉到它在我脑袋里四处探秘
Like... I don't know, I could feel it digging around in my head.
库珀 打开那扇门
Cooper, get to the door.
比如说我妈妈 我不知道 过世了
It's gonna be like my mum, I don't know, dead.
- 你妈妈 - 就像疯狂的荡秋千
- Your mum? - Fucking swinging from a fucking beam.
- 你妈妈不在里面 - 你根本控制不了这个
- Your mother is not in there. - You're not in control of this!
在我的脑子里  它他妈什么都知道  它知道
It's in my head. It fucking knows. It knows.
- 它知道 - 它知道什么
- It knows! - It knows what?
它知道我和我妈妈不和
It knows I got this thing with my mum.
库珀  我向你保证  她不在那里
Cooper, I promise you, she's not in there.
- 现在打开门 - 哦 我的天
- Now open the door. - Oh, my God.
这是我能带你离开的唯一方法  听我的
It's the only way I can get you out. Listen to me.
好的 好的  操  好的
Okay, Okay. Fuck. Okay.
无论里面是什么 不会伤害你的
Whatever's in there cannot harm you.
但如果你不打开那扇门 我没法让你出去 库珀
But I can't get you out unless you open that door, Cooper.
好的
Okay.
你能打开那扇门吗
Would you kindly open the door?
开始吧  走吧
Here we go. Here we go.
好的
Okay.
好的 好 我在房间里了  接入点在哪里
Okay, okay, I'm in the room. Where's the access point?
接入点
Access point?
- 没有接入点 - 什么
- There is no access point. - What?
我玩你呢  库珀
I'm fucking with you, Cooper.
我让你过来是为了检验 我们是否已经把你摧毁到足以
I told you to come up here to see if we've broken you enough
毫无疑问地遵守指令
to obey instructions without question.
- 而我们做到了 - 哦 不 不 不
- And we have. - Oh, no, no, no.
卡蒂 快  卡蒂 快 放我离开
Katie, come on. Katie, come on, let me out!
卡蒂 让我走啊 快啊  我了个擦
Katie, let me out, come on! What the fuck!
你打算做什么 你打算对我做什么
Oh, what are you gonna do? Oh, what are you doing to me?
- 为什么要这样做 - 你以为你将会见到你妈妈
- Why are you doing this? - You thought you'd see your mother.
- 操 - 她长什么样子
- Oh, fuck! - What does she look like?
你的妈妈 你能描述一下她的脸部吗
Your mother, can you describe her face?
她头发的颜色呢
Her hair colour?
她
She...
她高吗 矮吗 胖吗 瘦吗
Is she tall, short, fat, thin?
- 你在哪里长大 - 她
- Where did you grow up? - She...
你最喜欢的乐队是什么  你最喜欢的冰淇淋是什么口味的
What's your favourite band? Your favourite flavour ice cream?
那个用刀捅你的女孩叫什么
The name of the girl who stabbed you?
你什么都不知道了 是不是
You don't know any of these things, do you?
你不觉得这很古怪吗
Don't you think that's odd?
它在偷走我的记忆啊
It's fucking taking my memories!
用术语来说 这叫做重写数据
Overwriting them, technically.
操
Fuck.
往你身后的镜子里看
Look in the mirror behind you.
你能认出自己吗
Do you recognize yourself?
你还认识这个你正在看着的人吗
Do you even know who you're looking at?
不久之后你就什么都不是了  你会跟你爸爸一样
Soon you won't be anything. You'll be just like your dad.
闭嘴 闭嘴 闭嘴
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
- 这才是真正令你恐惧的 不是吗 - 别说了
- That's what really scares you, isn't it? - Stop it.
- 闭嘴  闭嘴  闭嘴  - 你会变得和他一样
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! - You're going the same place he did.
闭嘴  闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
- 你哪都去不了 - 闭嘴  别说了
- You're going nowhere. - Shut up! Shut up.
你本该打给妈妈的  她是你仅剩的一切
You should have called mum. She's all that's left.
- 你抛弃了她 - 不 不 不 不
- You abandoned her. - No, no, no, no!
从我脑子里滚出去
Get out of my head!
你永远也见不到她了  你永远也没法跟她说话了
You'll never see her again. You'll never speak to her again.
- 再也见不到她的面容 - 麻痹从我脑子里滚出去
- Never see her face. - Get out of my fucking head!
从他妈我的脑子里滚出去  滚出去
Get out of my fucking head! Get out of my fucking head!
你是个不肖子  你再也见不到你的母亲了
You're a bad son. You'll never see your mother again.
你哪也去不了
You're going nowhere.
人间蒸发
Straight into oblivion.
你活该  你本该给她打电话的
You deserve it. You should have called her.
从我脑子里给我滚出去
Get out of my fucking head!
把这玩意从我脑袋里弄出去  给我弄出去
Get it out of my head! Get it out of my head!
操 给我弄出去
Get it out of my fucking head!
库珀 我马上关闭它 好吗  我只需要连接上
Cooper, I'm gonna shut it off, okay? I just need to connect.
给我把它从脑子里弄出去
Get it out of my head!
弄出去  弄出去
Get it out of my head! Get it out of my head!
哦 我天  我在哪里
Oh, my God. Where am I?
你是谁
Who are you?
我没法停止程序
I can't stop it.
我不知道我是谁了  所以我 所以我得回家
I don't know who I am. So I... So I need to go home.
交互装置长出了根状的数据须
The interface has data tendrils like roots.
它们进入你意识的深度已经超出预期
They've dug in deeper than they're meant to.
穿透大脑 侵占整个区域 我没法停下它
Threaded through your brain, taken over whole areas, I can't stop it.
我没法移除它 也没法停下它
I can't remove it, and I can't stop it.
但是我 但是我不知道我是谁了
But I... But I don't know who I am.
我不知道 我不知道我是谁
I don't know... I don't know who I am.
我不知道我是谁了
I don't know who I am.
我不知道
I don't know.
我代表斋藤游戏团队 报以最诚挚的歉意
On behalf of Saito Game Team, I most humbly apologize.
你们是谁  你们对我做了什么
Who are you? What have you done to me?
- 你们对我做什么了 - 请把他和其他人放在一起
- What have you done to me? - Put him with the others, please.
不要 不 不 不  不要 不 不
No, no, no, no! No, no, no!
停 停 停 停下来  停 停 停下来
Stop, stop, stop, stop! Stop, stop, stop!
停 停 停 停  不 不要这样 不要
Stop, stop, stop, stop! No, don't, don't!
不要  不要啊
Don't! Don't!
- 停  停下来  - 不要
- Stop! Stop!  - No!
哦 我操
Oh, fuck.
才过了一秒钟
That was one second.
要么是他太敏感 要么就是软件太强大了
Either he's super susceptible to this or the software is way too powerful still.
在五毫秒之内从零跳至一万八
It's jumped from zero to 18K in five milliseconds...
我很抱歉  实际感受比理论预期强 库珀先生
I'm sorry. The experience was more powerful than intended, Mr. Cooper.
我希望你能原谅我们
I hope you can forgive us.
所有行李必须放在您前面的座位下
...all luggage under the seat in front of you.
现在必须关闭并收好所有的电子设备
All electronic devices should now be turned off and stowed
它们可能会影响飞机的导航和通信
as they may interfere with the aircraft's navigational and communication....
妈
Mum?
我得给他打电话
I have to call him.
妈
Mum?
库珀为什么走了
Why did Cooper go?
- 我 - 妈 我就在这里啊  我是
- I... - Mom, I'm right here. I'm...
- 我就在这里啊 妈妈 - 我得给库珀打电话
- I'm right here, Mum. - I have to call Cooper.
我得给他打电话 确认他是否安全
I have to call and make sure that he's safe.
我得打给他  我得打给他  我得打给他
I have to call him. I have to call him. I have to call him.
妈妈
Mum?
妈
Mum!
妈妈  妈妈  妈妈  妈妈
Mum! Mum! Mum! Mum!
- 发生了什么  - 他的手机响了
- 你不是收走他的手机了吗  - 是的 但是
- 信号会干扰的  - 我记得把手机关了的
可能是我离开房间的时候 他做了些什么
是我疏忽了  以后不会再犯了
输入的信号肯定干扰了上传了序列
他大脑中的每一个突触都点亮了
接着他就这样死了
你说他喊了 喊了什么
“妈”
"Mum."
- 做一下记录  - 好的
(库珀·雷德菲尔德)
(手机信号干扰)
(观察报告)
(叫了“妈妈”)